# Omar Waleed Zenhom



## **Contact**

#### Address:

Egypt - Giza - 6th of October

### Phone:

+201155240556

#### **Email:**

Omarwaleedzenhom2002@gmail .com

# Languages

Arabic – Native language English – Good German – intermediate

# **Summary**

Senior Web Developer specializing in front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, C++ OOP, JavaScript, CSS. Background in project management and customer relations. I am a beginner in the Flutter programming language. I created the front-end of applications

# **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Problem Solving
- Code tester
- All Microsoft office Family
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- Fast learner
- Make desicions

# **Experience**

Web Developer - 09/2021 to now Freelancer, Websites

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front-end public and internal websites.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

**Graphic designer** - 01/2018 to now **Freelancer**, Websites **Resale**, Organization

- I worked on the Photoshop program in training teams at the Resala Foundation. I created many different designs for all social media sites, which later helped me to adapt this programming skill and create good user interfaces.
- I also worked with many institutions and student activities in the work of designs, **such as:** 
  - Science land, Turning Point, SIT

# Omar Waleed Zenhom



## **Contact**

## **Address:**

Egypt - Giza - 6th of October

### Phone:

+201155240556

#### **Email:**

Omarwaleedzenhom2002@gmail. com

# Languages

Arabic – Native language English – Good German – intermediate

## **Social Contact**





LinkedIn

YouTube

# **Experience**

Montage - 05/2021 to now **Freelancer**, Websites

- I'm a good of Adobe's editing software such as:
  - Adobe Photoshop
  - o Adobe Premiere Pro
    - I learned montage to produce videos on YouTube, I made many videos.
  - Adobe After Effects
  - Adobe InDesign
  - Adobe illustrator
  - Adobe XD
  - Adobe Flash Player

Montage - 01/2007 to 01/2015 Nahdet Misr Company, Egypt

> At this time, I worked on animating the animation on the Adobe Flash Player program and creating a CD that came with the books produced by the company

## **Education**

In the second year: Faculty of Computing and Artificial

Intelligence- 2022 Cairo University, Egypt

## **Certifications**

Adobe Programs (certificate): **Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effect**.

Programming Languages: **HTML5, C++ OOP, CSS, Flutter, Dart**. Microsoft Programs: **All Microsoft office Family.** ICDL

# **Communication Skills**

- The ability to practice the skill of communication between colleagues.
- The ability to exercise team leadership to achieve the required goal.
- The ability to professionally design and present information.
- The ability to make decisions and solve problems